Everyone is leaning on you, but if
you give up, who will pick you up?  This got
me thinking.  In family, at work, in
other people's problems, all of you.  But what
if you're the one who's sick, is there anyone prepared
for you?  Because sometimes the
mindset is like this.  I have an HMO, I have a job
, I have savings.  So
you think it's okay.  But with
just one serious illness, everyone can pose
.  What you saved for 10 years
can be wiped out by a single hospital bill.
Especially for our aging
ops, this is not to scare you, but
critical illness can happen, it ca
n't.  But when it comes,
you must be ready.  That's why I want to share
Manolife Health Flex with you.  It
starts at Php83 a day only.  You are now secure
because you have 100 plus critical
illness coverage.  Especially if
you have a history of cancer, heart attack or
stroke, that is covered.  And in case
you are diagnosed with an early stage critical
illness, you will immediately receive a 25% cash benefit
.  And when
he progresses to the advance stage, you can claim
the full 100% lums cash benefit.  And
of course, if you're working and you're
absent from work for a long time, he has a daily
hospital income allowance.  So you have
income replacement that you can use
for extra.  What's even better is that it has a
recovery benefit feature.  If
you are diagnosed with an advanced critical
illness, you will receive 24 months of
monthly cash benefits while
you recover.  It also has a long
life bonus feature.  With this long life
bonus, he earns annual
dividends that you can withdraw
anytime.  Or you can leave it until it
matures or accumulates
over time.  You have the option to pay
it in installments of 5 years, 10 years, or you can
also extend it up to 60 years.  It depends on
whether you want to extend
your cash flow or the dividend.  Get it
for as low as Php83 per day.  Did you know
that for just Php83 per day,
a 30-year-old individual could be covered with
1 million critical illness coverage?
So if you want to personalize
this plan for yourself, just use the link on
my bio or message me or just
comment in the comment section.  This is
Bench and I'm your insurance partner.  M.